If you desire a fresh and youthful look, a look that you have lost due to sagging skin,
loss of volume and accentuation of wrinkles, a face lift is the right option for you.
I will explain why. A face lift goes far beyond lifting the skin.
When we perform this procedure, we also mobilize the layer of tissue that covers, invests,
and connects the muscles of the face and neck, also known as the SMAS layer.
Lifting this layer allows us to achieve a natural and harmonious improvement
in the appearance of the skin and also in the expression of the face.
In this way, the result is much more durable. In addition, we can use advanced
filler techniques to give volume to areas that have lost it and get an even more powerful
result in the youthfulness that the face reflects. The vast majority of our patients
says that they feel that they have rejuvenated ten years in time. That is the case of Caroline,
whose photos you are watching right now and with whom we achieved this magnificent result.
However, due to the complexity of the facial tissue and the large number of nerves that the
face has, it is extremely important that this procedure will be performed by a board-certified
plastic surgeon. Let me introduce myself. I'm Dr. Fulvio Correa, a board-certified plastic surgeon.
Through our all-inclusive program that we have designed especially for patients
come from other countries like you. My staff will accompany you in every phase of the journey,
answering all your questions, helping you to plan your trip, scheduling your accommodation in
our recovery house, where you will have all the comforts and care necessary for a prompt
and satisfactory recovery. Schedule your free evaluation right now and start your journey
to achieve your goals and boost your confidence.